gravitypope.com 2013-06-07

# gravitypope

**PRIVACY POLICY  
**

Gravitypope is committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors to our web site. The following policy describes how gravitypope collects, protects and uses information it receives from visitors to the web site. 

**Purchasing on gravitypope.com.**  
When you purchase a product on the site, we need you to provide your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number. This allows us to provide a faster method for users to receive the products desired.

**Online c ontest or promotion.**  
When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, gravitypope may ask for the visitor's name, address, e-mail address and telephone number so that they are able to better administer the contest and notify winners.

We may also use the information we collect during the registration process to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, special offers, and new product information we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, or would like to opt-out of any other information request or distribution, please contact us at [mailorder@gravitypope.com](mailto:mailorder@gravitypope.com) for assistance. 

**P rotection of visitor information?**  
We employ industry recognized security safeguards to protect the personal information that you have provided to us from loss, misuse and unauthorized alteration. Whenever you transmit sensitive information, such as a credit card number, to us through our website, we provide you access to a secure server that allows 128 bit encryption of your data. Your credit card number is never transmitted over the Internet so you don't have to worry about it being seen by third parties while in transit. Your information is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems.

**V isitor information and outside parties?**  
Gravitypope does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer outside the company personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily provide in any registration or contest submission. This information is used to better understand visitors' to our site and to support related transactions made on the site. 

We may use e-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information to contact visitors who communicate with us. For example, we may direct e-mail to visitors who provide us with their e-mail addresses for specific purposes such as receiving our e-mail newsletters, information, or being notified if they have won one of our contests. Each e-mail newsletter always contains instructions on how to discontinue receipt of the newsletter. However, if a visitor at anytime chooses to no longer receive such information and opt-out from any future mailings, please contact us at [mailorder@gravitypope.com](mailto:mailorder@gravitypope.com) to do so.

**Your consent**  
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information as described above by www.gravitypope.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
